china-airlines.com 2018-12-23

# Information Security Policy | China Airlines

## Collection of Customer Information

We will collect your personal information through the following methods in certain parts of the Website, Mobile APP, Ticketing counter or Service Center:

  1. Applying for Dynasty Flyer Program (DFP) Membership
  2. Online booking/ticketing
  3. Booking Inquiry and additional purchase or service
  4. Airport processing includes checking procedure or luggage services
  5. YesTrip trip advisory
  6. DFP interactive services and travel information provided for members
  7. Messaging service
  8. Online shopping and activities
  9. Promotion and marketing
  10. Customer service

Through the above collection methods, we may collect your personal information, including but not limited to following categories:

  1. Personal identifiers
  2. Identifiers of personal finance
  3. Identifiers issued by government agencies
  4. Personal details
  5. Details of the member’s family members
  6. Travel and other migration details
  7. Leisure activities and hobbies
  8. Occupations
  9. Compensations
  10. Health records
  11. Personal identifiers of children
  12. Uncategorized information

And the content might include but not limited to

Title, Chinese and English name on your passport, date of birth, nationality, ID number, passport number, country of residence, mailing address, email address, phone number, fax number, mobile number, DFP membership card number and password, credit card information (including owner name, card number, and card expiration date), company name, company address, profession and position, assignees' name and DFP membership card number, preferred language, special diets and seat and travel preferences, health record and children information, IP and cookies, other material includes audio or paper recordings from customer service and other information might directly or indirectly identify persons. If you fail to provide the required personal information, certain parts of the requested online services may be unavailable.

China Airlines may also occasionally ask you to update your personal data. Your booking information or flight itinerary plan may be disclosed to the customs and immigration related authorities in accordance with the provisions of the law. Therefore, it is very important to ensure that the personal data in your booking details or flight itinerary plan is up-to-date, complete and correct.

China Airlines needs your assistance to ensure that your personal information is up-to-date, complete and correct. Therefore, if your personal data changes, please contact China Airlines and provide your updated customer information. If you are a Dynasty frequent flyer program member or a registered website user, you can update your personal information at any time by logging in to your account on the China Airlines website.

## Use of Customer Information

Customer information will be used for business management purpose only and is aimed at improving service quality and providing enhanced personal service for customers:

  1. Online ticketing services including customized services, check-in and provide related information
  2. Evaluate and handle DFP membership applications
  3. Operate DFP services, including mileage accumulation, DFP membership records, mileage redemption records, and mileage transfer records
  4. Handle members' trip arrangement and the products and services purchased including online shopping, pre-orders.
  5. Handle online services, message notification service, discount service, and promotion service for members
  6. Market surveys and questionnaires for services improvement
  7. We may provide your information collected by us to our affiliated companies, subsidiaries, and other business partners including but not limited to Co-Brand Card banks so that they can process the information and provide related services to you.

We promise that we will not reveal your personal information to any third parties not related to this service or transaction without your consent.

When you book or purchase travel-related products (car rental, hotel, local transportation or others) sold by other providers on this website, these providers may collect your personal information through their transaction platform to provide subsequent services. Personal information might be used by our worldwide branches and ticketing counters to provide subsequent services.

The period of use of the personal data mentioned above is based on the duration of collection of the specified purpose, or as determined by relevant laws or the period of preservation necessary for the execution of the business or on a contractual basis.
